They're back to raise a little terror.
Hotel Transylvania 2 is a animation, comedy, family
film directed by Genndy Tartakovsky.
When the old-old-old-fashioned vampire Vlad arrives at the hotel for an impromptu family get-together,
Hotel Transylvania is in for a collision of supernatural old-school and modern day cool.
Dracula (voice), played by Adam Sandler.
Johnny Loughran (voice), played by Andy Samberg.
Mavis Dracula (voice), played by Selena Gomez.
Frankenstein (voice), played by Kevin James.
Wayne (voice), played by Steve Buscemi.
Griffin (voice), played by David Spade.
Hotel Transylvania 2 is a 2015 American animated monster comedy film directed by
Genndy Tartakovsky and written by Robert Smigel and Adam Sandler.
Produced by Columbia Pictures and Sony Pictures Animation, it is the second installment in
the Hotel Transylvania franchise and the sequel to Hotel Transylvania (2012).
Sandler, Andy Samberg, Selena Gomez, Kevin James, David Spade, Steve Buscemi, Molly Shannon and Fran Drescher
reprise their roles from the first film, with Keegan-Michael Key and Mel Brooks joining the cast.
The film takes place several years after the events of the first film.
Mavis and Johnny have a young son named Dennis, whose lack of any vampire abilities
worries both Mavis and his maternal grandfather Dracula for differing reasons.
When Mavis and Johnny travel to Johnny's hometown in Santa Cruz, California, Drac calls
his friends to help him make Dennis a vampire, much to Mavis's dismay.
Hotel Transylvania 2 was released theatrically on
September 25, 2015, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received mixed reviews and grossed $474
million worldwide on an $80 million budget.
It won a Kids' Choice Award for Favorite Animated Movie.
A further sequel, Hotel Transylvania 3: Summer Vacation, was released in 2018.
The film explores themes of hotel, witch, skeleton, magic, transylvania.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.